Guide to the Nicole Di Bona Peterson Collection of Advertising Cookbooks, 1850s-2000s
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University, Durham, N.C., USA
- Scottish Cookbooks 1900s-1990s, 28
  - Scotch Whisky Recipes, 1991 (Box INTL A03, Item SCOT-A-0004)
    Company: Scotch Whisky Heritage Centre
    Product: Scotch whisky
    Note: color and black-and-white photographs, some historical
- South African Cookbooks 1940s-1960s, 29
  - How to Enjoy a Wobble with Royal, circa 1960s (Box INTL A03, Item SOAF-A-0001)
    Company: Royal Baking Powder (Pty.) Ltd.
    Note: color and black-and-white photographs, stand up back
  - How to bake the Royal way, circa 1940s (Box INTL C04, Item SOAF-C-001)
  - Royal's Baking Mix easy as ABC, circa 1940s (Box INTL C04, Item SOAF-C-002)
    Product: Royal Baking Powder, Baking-Mix
  - Royal Festival of Jellies, circa 1950s (Box INTL C04, Item SOAF-C-003)
    Company: Royal
    Product: Royal Jelly
- Spanish Cookbooks 1962, 30
  - Olive Oil from Spain: A Short Book of Recipes, 1962 (Box INTL A03, Item SPAIN-A-0001)
    Company: Institute for the Foreign Publicity of Olive Products, Sindicato Nacional del Olivo
    Product: Olive oil
- Missing Cookbooks, 31
  - Recipes: Refreshing Fruit Sherbets and Water Ices made with 'Junket' Sherbet Mix, 1948
    Product: Junket sherbet mix
  - You've Got It Made with Bisquick CookBook: Dinnertime Recipes Made in under 15 Minutes, circa 1990s (1980s?)
    Product: Bisquick Buttermilk Baking Mix
    Note: Poor condition. Illustrations of women in many situations: too busy with children, gardening, exercise, etc. to cook.
  - Jell-O: The Girl in February, 1930s
  - This is the story of Heinz Rice Flakes, 1930s
  - Florida Mamey Recipes, 1986
    Company: J. R. Brooks & Son Inc.
    Product: Florida Mamey
    Note: Exotic fruit, some history
  - Kenmore Barbecue Equipment, 1958
    Note: Man cooking on grill, wife and son standing nearby
  - Modern Methods of Home Canning, circa 1940s
  - Home Baking Made Easy for Beginners and Experts, 1953
    Note: Color cover illustration of mother and daughter cooking together, illustrations of food preparation.
  - Decorating made easy for everyone, circa 1960s
    Product: Pillsbury Cake and Cookie Decorator
    Note: Not really a cookbook – illustrated pamphlet demonstrating ways to use icing in a spray can.
  - Kenmore Microwave Cooking, 1979
  - The Casserole Cook Book, 1956
  - The Food Processor Cookbook, 1979
  - [unknown], circa 1980s
    Product: Rum, Maple Leaf meat products, Pam cooking spray, Catelli pasta, Taster's choice, etc.
    Note: No cover. Bilingual (French and English)
  - California Wine Cookery and Drinks, 1960